Emil Bertholdsson

Master of Science in Media Technology and Engineering

Hi! I love developing fun experiences in both web and game development. I enjoy solving complex problems with a passion for games and UI/UX design and games. I recently graduated university as a Master of Science in Media Technology and Engineering.











Emil Bertholdsson emilbert.github.io github.com/EmilBert +46723161811 emil.bertholdsson@gmail.com

Skills in C++, C#, PYTHON, HTML, CSS, JS, TS, SQL, React, OpenGL, Unity, VR, FIGMA

Education

Linköping Technical University

M.Sc Computer Science and Engineering in Media Technology

• B.Sc Computer Science and Engineering in Media Technology

Berzeliusskolan

• High school degree in Information and Media technology

September 2021 - August 2023 September 2018 - June 2021

September 2015 - June 2018

Experience

StoneTech Games - Indie Game Studio

Co-Founder, Gameplay Programmer & Lead UI/UX Designer

- Responsible for UI/UX-design and implementation
- Creating solutions for larger-scale game project
- Iterative development & UX testing.

Linköping Technical University

LiTHehack - Mentor in Programming

- Helped 30+ students with programming questions and problems
- Communicating & Teaching problem solving

CoderDojo Norrköping - Volunteer work at a non-profit organization

Dojo- & Coach-responsible (Board-member)

- Further develop activities after feedback
- Plan and organize events for upwards of 20 attendees at a time

Norrköping, Sweden

August 2022 - Ongoing

Norrköping, Sweden September 2021 - June 2022

> Norrköping, Sweden June 2021 - June 2023

Dev Projects

Holmgang - C#, Unity Game Engine

Made in a group of 4, 2nd place at LiU Game Awards

Gameplay Programmer, UI/UX designer

- C# and Unity programming
- · Video game design patterns
- Procedural Generation with Wave Function Collapse

Procedural Voxel Terrain - C++, OpenGL

Solo project

- 2D and 3D Noise application
- 3D rendering using OpenGL

Barker Social Media - React, TS, MongoDB, Node

Made in a group of 4

Fullstack devoloper, Web designer

- Backend and Frontend development
- · Web design and Figma prototyping
- Agile methods

The Space Gasstation - SteamVR, Unity Game Engine

Made in a group of 4

Game developer, narrative- and game designer

- C# and Unity programming
- Immersive VR game development

August 2022 - October 2022

October 2021 - January 2022

September 2022 - june 2022

October 2021 - December 2021